McLaren, Eugene; Papers ua902.031
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Research Material, 1949-1990; Undated; 2; 3.2 cubic ft.
  - Fog Proposal, Original, 1984-1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Fog Proposal, References, 1982; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Fog Proposal, Revisions, 1985; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Fog Project Proposal Drafts, 1985-1986; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 6)
  - Fog Water Deposition Outline and Draft, 1984; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 7)
  - Forest Atmosphere Interaction Workshop, 1985; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Forest Ecology of Ice Storms, ASRC Publication, 1961 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Gas Particle Reactions and Conversions, 1970-1971; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Gaseous Electrics Conference at SUNY Albany, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Heterogeneous Chemistry in the Atmosphere, Vienna Conference, 1983-1984; 1991; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Intermedia Transport Research Center, Coop Agreement, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Information on Clouds, Rain, Fog, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 14)
  - International Conference on Condensation Nuclei, 1966 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 15)
  - Jaeschke Notes and Correspondence, 1985; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 16)
  - Kinetics of Oxidation of SO2 in Water, 1980 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 17)
  - "Lake Effect" Storm Studies, 1962; 1971; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 18)
  - LRTAAP Conference Notes, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Long Range Transport of Airborne Pollutants, 1980-1981; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 20)
  - McLaren, Eugene, Published Works and Papers, 1954-1959; 1971-1973; 1982-1989; 1990; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 21)
  - Multiphase Processors Relevant to Atmospheric Chemistry Conference, 1981 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Narakov's Proposal, 1983; 1985; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Natural Sciences Institute, ASRC Summer Program, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 24)
  - 1st National Conference on Weather Modification, 1968 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Notes on the Nature of the Adsorption of SO2 on Flyash, ASRC Publication, Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Northern Arizona Research Trip, 2nd Annual Report, 1970 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 27)
  - NSF Proposal, Measurements of Soluble Atmosphere Trace Gasses, 1982; Undated (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Oxidation of SO2 on Certain Carbon Particulates, 1983 (Box 2 (2-Research Material), Folder 29)
  - Project Cirrus, 1953 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 1)
  - References, 1983-1984; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Rensselaerville, 1961; 1968; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 3)
  - Role of Dew in Atmosphere Pollution Deposition, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 4)
  - Role of Condensation Process in Pollutant Deposition, 1980 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 5)
  - Sarasota, NASA Workshop Notes, 1984; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 6-7)
  - Schaefer, GE Reports, 1949-1950; 1970 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 8)
  - Schenectady City Hall Marble Deterioration Study, 1982 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 9)
  - Research Proposal, Silver Iodide, 1962-1963; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 10)
  - Use of Single Particle Counters to Acquire Spatial Inhomogeneities of Particulate Clouds, ASRC Publication, 1981 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 11)
  - Study Proposal for Strong Acid in Clouds, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 12)
  - Surface Area, Data and Calculations, 1982-1983; 1985; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 13)
  - Tulla Deposition, 1984-1985; 1990; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 14)
  - US-European Collaboration, 1984-1985; 1987; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 15)
  - US-Italian Collaboration, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 16)
  - US-Germany, Coop Project, 1985 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 17)
  - Weather Modification Research Proposal, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 18)
  - Weather Modification Conference Report, 1974 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 19)
  - Weather Modification Conference Proposal Development, 1973-1974; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 20)
  - Weather Modification Report, 1974-1975 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 21)
  - Whiteface Mountain and Adirondack Conference, 1958; 1963 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 22)
  - Whiteface Mountain Conference, 1962; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 23)
  - Whiteface Mountain Summer Program, ASRC Publication, 1961-1962; 1964; 1971 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 24)
  - Whiteface Mountain Air Chemistry Retreat, 1978; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 25)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Seminar, 1961-1962 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 26)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Trip Notes, 1961-1963; Undated (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 27)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1963-1964 (Box 3 (2-Research Material), Folder 28)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1965-1966 (Box 4 (2-Research Material), Folder 1)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1967-1998 (Box 4 (2-Research Material), Folder 2)
  - Yellowstone Field Research Expedition, 1969-1971 (Box 4 (2-Research Material), Folder 3)